24小时
第三季  第二集
前情提要
托尼 有人抛下一具感染了病毒的尸体
Tony, someone just dropped out a dead body infected with the virus.
根据验尸结果 一周后
Based on the autopsy, at the end of the first week,
9%的洛杉矶人口会被感染
9% of the Los Angeles county would be infected.
那是一百多万人啊
It's over a 1 million people.
放了拉姆·萨拉扎
We want the release of Ramon Salazar.
如果你们拒绝 病毒就会散播
If you refuse to comply, the virus will be unleashed.
杰克 你最了解萨拉扎的情况
Jack, you know Salazar better than anybody else here.
你觉得这是谁干的?
Who do you think we're dealing with?
毫无疑问是他兄弟 二把手赫克托
Without a doubt his brother. Hector was next in command.
拉姆被逮住后 他躲了起来
He went underground the second Ramon was taken into custody.
给FBI打电话了吗?
Have you made the call to the FBI?
打了
Yes, I did.
那个男孩呢?
What about our boy?
我正监视着他
I'm watching him now.
你做什么了? 贩毒?
What are you into here man? You're selling dope?
有人付了我五千美元 要我把毒品带入境
This guy he paid me $5000 to bring some coke over the border.
就在昨晚
I did that last night.
今天我把毒品送过去 又得了五千美元
Today, I drop it off, I get another $5000.
FBI什么时候接到的电话?
When did FBI get this call?
20分钟前
About 20 minutes ago.
我们还不知道是谁干的?
And we don't know who we're dealing with?
电话从外线打来 声音经过了处理
It was a scrambled voice on an open line.
要取消辩论吗?
Do we cancel the debate?
他们在讨论我们是否需要离开洛杉矶
They are discussing whether or not we should stay in Los Angeles.
蔡斯 没哪天是合适的
Chase, no day is a good day.
我们说过两个月后还没分手 就跟他坦白
We said it we will tell him if we're still together after two months.
都快三个月了
It's almost three.
为什么还不告诉他?
Why don't we just tell him and get it over with?
听着杰克
Listen Jack.
你接近萨拉扎有6个月
You were under of Salazar for 6 months.
我知道发生了什么 你看起来很糟
I know what they did to you. You look like hell.
我很担心你哦 杰克
I'm concerned about you, Jack.
为了抓我你所做的事 我不想告诉别人
The things you did to get me here, I wouldn't wish on anyone.
知道是谁干的后 总统才会做决定...
The president is not gonna make any decisions until he knows what we're dealing with so...
托尼 把所有情况告诉我
give me all the parameters Tony.
我们收到一个恐怖分子的威胁电话
Well, basically, what we have here is a terrorist demand.
拉姆·萨拉扎的亲信打来的 估计是他兄弟赫克托
Someone close to Ramon Salazar, we're guessing his brother, Hector,
要求我们释放他
is demanding his release.
如果拒绝 他威胁说要散播一种快速致死的病毒
If we don't comply, he's threatening to initiate an operate of a very deadly fast acting virus.
怎样判定他们拥有此病毒?
How do we know if these people are really in possession of it?
韦恩 今天桑尼 马切尔博士来了电话
Wayne, I've got Dr.Sunny Macer on the line.
她是卫生部的技术指导 我让她来说
She is technical director of National Health Services. I let her address that.
帕默尔先生 一小时前
Mr Palmer, about an hour ago,
有人将一具尸体抛在我们部门外面
a dead body was anonymously delivered to our office.
尸体被人植入了3号类型的免疫病毒
It was infected with a type 3 immuno-virus deliberatery introduced into its system.
症状出现后24小时内致人死亡 且无药可治无药可防
This virus kills within 24 hours of exposure and there is no none antidote or vaccin.
尤其可怕的是 病毒传播速度之快
What's particurlaly disturbing is how fast it spreads.
请看
Take a look.
如你们看到的
As you can see,
几小时的潜伏期内无症状
it's latent for several hours,
但一旦症状出现后
but once the symptoms present,
它迅速侵蚀宿主
it consumes the host rapidly.
我们部门会发给你们 如果病毒被散播
Our office will be sending you preliminary projections of casualties
初期会受感染人数的估计
in case something like this should be unleashed.
韦恩 这数目相当庞大
And Wayne, I've gotta tell you, it's pretty bleak.
我不明白
I don't understand this.
我们知道什么才算是生化威胁
I mean, I thought we knew what biological threats were out there.
我们怎么这么急着要掐灭
And how do we find ourselves up against the wall so suddenly
这连苗头都没出现的事?
with something that isn't even on our radar?
这是一种前所未见的病毒
This is a strain we've never seen.
验尸结果证实 有人蓄意培育了些病毒
The autopsy is confirming that someone is engineered this virus
使它们的致死性比原基因快十倍
to kill 10 times faster than its ordinary genotypes.
嗯 我明白了
Ok. Ok, I see.
长官 我无法估计如果恐怖分子散播了病毒
Sir, I can't underscore enough how potentially devastating
会造成多么大的破坏
it would be if this virus were released by terrorists.
了解这些后 总统会做什么样的决定?
By giving this information, what options would the President be looking at?
美国在面对恐怖分子威胁的时候
It's the unweathering policy of the USA to stand firm
绝对不会妥协动摇
against any terrorists demands.
托尼 我了解总统
And I know the President, Tony,
不管受到什么威胁
He will not free Salazar.
他都不会释放萨拉扎
No matter what the threat.
我们没时间讨论这些原则问题
All right then we can't waste any time on standard protocole today.
我们只剩下5小时
We've been giving five hours to comply.
如果要找到凶犯 阻止阴谋
If we're gonna find these people and stop this threat
反恐小组需要大量的资源
then CTU has to have any possible resources at its disposal.
没问题
You'll have it.
好 如果没别的事 我们组要马上回去工作
All right. Now if we've nothing else to discuss, I'd like to get my team back to work.
-了解  -谢谢
-Understood.  -Thank you.
我是鲍尔
Bauer.
爸 是我
Dad, it's me.
什么事 金?
What, Kim?
我和亚当在死者身上发现些东西
Adam and I just found something on Goss.
我们正在调查 很快就能为你查到地址了
We're working it up now. We should have an address for you pretty soon.
干得好
Ok, good work.
爸... 记得吗 我有话想和你谈
And... Dad, remember, I want to talk to you.
嗯? 怎么了?
What? Something wrong?
没什么 我想上去和你谈
No. I was just wondering if I could come up for a few minutes.
是私事
Something personal.
宝贝 现在可不太合适
Sweetheart, right now is not a good time.
我有时间就下去找你 好吗?
As soon as I've got a moment I'll come down, ok?
好 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
查到了更多戈斯的信息
They're getting close to Goss.
你刚才没注射毒品吧?
You didn't shoot up, did you?
怎么? 你以为瞒得住我?
What? You think you'll hide it from me?
我不是要瞒你
I am not trying to hide it from you.
我在努力戒掉!
I am trying to quit!
戒掉还不够 杰克
Ok, people don't just quit Jack.
我一直情绪不佳
I've been tempering off.
好 我现在控制住了
OK, now it's time to stop.
看起来不像控制住了
It doesn't look like it's time.
算了 今天并不是
All right, today is not a good day for you
调整心情的好时机
to be needing a fix.
为什么不去帮克萝伊做点事
Why don't you go work with Chloe
找找赫克托 萨拉扎的窝点?
and see if you can pin down a location on Hector Salazar?
镇定剂疗法有何不妥?
What's wrong with the methadone program?
它是要花点时间 但能起作用
Ok, it takes a little time but it works.
我不想留下毒瘾记录 你懂吗?
I am not going on record with this addiction, do you understand me?
现在你是唯一知道此事的人 不要告诉别人
OK, so right now, you're the only person who knows about it. It's gonna stay that way.
但这不是令人羞耻的事
OK, this is nothing to be ashamed of.
你为了职责才这样做的
You did this in the line of duty.
只有这样才能接近萨拉扎
Doing junk whas the only to get close to Salazar
没有人会因此指责你
Nobody is gonna knock you for that.
我知道我做过什么 蔡斯 不谈了
I know what I did, Chase. This conversation is over.
回去工作吧
Just get back to work.
好吧
Yeah.
蔡斯?
Chase?
干嘛?
What?
我刚看了卫生部提供的资料录相
I was just looking at playback of the Health Services briefing.
怎么了?
What about it?
政府不会看着灾难发生吧?
The government is not letting this happen, are they?
萨拉扎再坏 也只是个人而已
I mean Salazar is just one person no matter how bad he is.
不用管那些克萝伊 我们只需要遵照命令
Free it all that Chloe. We need to operate under orders
找出病毒的携带者
that is to find the carrier of this virus.
找出携带者? 就4个小时?
Find the carrier? In the next 4 hours?
得了 蔡斯! 这是不可能的事
Come on Chase! That's not likely, is it?
如果我们只坐在这儿讨论 当然不可能
Not if we sit here and debate it.
谁负责查找戈斯的事情
Who is just supposed to find and modify the list of Goss' associates?
金正在做
Kim is bringing it up now.
好 检查验尸报告 看有没漏掉的细节
Great. Then, go over the autopsy report. See if there's anything they overlooked.
好
Fine.
这是关于戈斯的资料
Here are the files on Goss.
刚才我在上面 听见你和你爸的对话
I heard you talking to your dad when I was in his office.
为什么想今天告诉他?
Why do you want to tell him today?
因为这不是件大事
Because it's not a big deal.
这就是件大事 好吗? 我不仅是他手下
Well, it is a big deal, ok? Now not only do I work for him
还是个外勤探员
but I'm also a field agent.
他最不喜欢这样的人当他女儿男友
It's the last thing he wants for his daughter.
你怎么知道?
How do you know that?
我就是知道
I know.
他跟我聊过
Ok? I mean, he talks about things.
他说总是没时间陪着你
About how he was never there for you,
和你妈妈...
or you mum...
他认为一个外勤探员没资格
Ok? He doesn't believe that a field agent can have
拥有一段恋情
a relationship outside of work.
你没想过 也许我们的事会令他开心?
Well, did you ever start to think that maybe it would make him happy?
他女儿找到了真爱?
That his daughter has found someone she loves?
听着 我也爱你
Look, I love you too. Ok?
但今天真的不合适
I just don't think today is a good day.
蔡斯 帮我复印那份名单
Chase, I need you to copy me on that list.
这是什么文件?
Ok, what's this column?
嗯... 他的家庭情况 合法的
Hmm...That's family and that's legal.
-很好  -好
-Great.  -Ok.
我明白 仔细将这些文件和拉美的文件进行交叉对比
Yeah, I understand but just watch to cross-reference those files with our Latin America files.
是的 把所有名单打印出来
Yes. I want all the names to printed out.
送到我办公室 谢谢
Ok. Just give that over to my office. Thanks.
-嗨 爸!  -嗨 宝贝
-Hey, Dad!  -Hey, sweetheart.
你还好吗?
You're all right?
很好 有什么事?
Yeah. Well, what's going on?
蔡斯说你压力很大
Chase said you were really stressed out.
压力 你指... 你指什么"压力"?
Stressed, what do... what do... what do you mean'stressed'?
你知道...
You know...
萨拉扎和恐怖分子的威胁
Salazar and the terrorists threat.
是的
Yeah.
是的! 但我能控制事态 我只是太忙了
Yeah! Yeah but I think we gonna get it under control. We just got a lot of work to do.
现在能和你谈谈吗?
Listen, can I talk to you now?
当然可以 进来吧
Yeah, yeah sure, come in.
坐吧
Take a seat.
怎么回事?
Hey, what's going on?
经历过这么多事后
After all we've been through,
我不想再对你有所隐瞒...
I find it very difficult to keep things from you...
什么事?
Ok, what's up?
蔡斯和我交往有一段时间了
Chase and I have been going out for a while
我们是认真的
and it's starting to get serious.
我... 我知道他想亲自告诉你
I mean... I think he wanted to be the one to tell you
但他怕影响你们之间的关系
but he was worried that it would cause a problem between you two.
我明白了...
I see...
你们在一起多久了?
How long are the two of you been seeing each other?
三个月
Three months.
我非常喜欢他 爸
I really care for him dad.
你觉得怎样?
So what do you think?
我不知道怎样
I don't know what I think.
我很吃惊
I'm really surprised.
对不起 今天发生的事让我有些心烦意乱...
And, I'm sorry, I'm a little bit distracted with everything that's going on today but...
我知道...
I know but...
没关系 我只是想让你知道
Forget it. I just had to let you know.
不 不 我很高兴你能告诉我
No, no, I'm glad you told me.
好
Ok.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
-I love you.  -I love you too.
我跟他说了
I told him.
他说什么?
What did he say?
什么都没说
Nothing.
-德斯勒  -米歇尔 我是桑尼
-Dessler.  -Michelle, it's Sunny.
我有些发现 也许对你们有用
I think I found something that might be helpful to your guys.
什么发现?
What's that?
我说过戈斯的身体里有些奇怪的东西...
I told you I found something odd in Goss's system...
我们找到一个未变形的病毒分子
We found an unmetabolised virus particle.
通俗地说 病毒似乎包含在晶状物中
I'll skip techno-babble. Bottom line: It looks like the virus was delivered in a crystalline form.
也许病毒就在白粉中
I mean, maybe what you're looking for is a white powder.
可能是一包可卡因或海洛因?
So, it would look like a bag of cocaine or heroin?
对 也许这是他们的诡计
Yeah, that may be the strategy.
毒贩以为自己在贩毒品
Someone thinks that they're selling a bag of coke
而其实是在运病毒
well in fact they're handling a virus.
凯尔 那事我不干 懂吗?
Look, Kyle, I'm not gonna do it, ok?
不管你给我多少钱 这是在偷窃毒品
I don't care how much you pay me, it's stealing drugs.
蒂姆 你是我最好的朋友
Tim, you're my best friend.
来吧 来帮我
Come on, you've gotta come. Do it for me.
凯尔 你去墨西哥拿毒品前 应该告诉我!
Well, look Kyle, you should talked to me before you went down to Mexico and bought a bag of coke!
我... 你只需要坐在车里等 我去交货
I'm not... I'm not asking you to do anything but wait in the car. I'll make the delivery.
我不去 不会和你一起去
I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna go with you.
好吧
Fine.
喂
Yeah.
凯尔 我是扎克
Kyle, it's Zack.
你好扎克! 什么事?
Zack, hey! What's up?
-我们得谈谈  -稍等 伙计
-We need to talk.  -Hold on a second, man.
谁是扎克?
Who's Zack?
不是谁
It's nobody.
你俩今天怎么了? 搞得神神秘秘
What's with you guys today? Everything is a secret.
他在处理些家务事
He's got family stuff going on.
什么事 伙计?
What's going on, man?
你跟我说! 你拿到了白粉?
You tell me! You've got the powder?
对 我当然拿到了
Yeah, yeah, of course I do.
什么时候送过去
Just tell me when to drop it off.
今晚 7:30左右
Tonight. Come by around 7:30.
7:30 好的
7:30, yeah.
再重说一遍好吗? 我... 怎样交货?
Can we just go over one more time? I'd like... how this all thing is gonna go down?
还重复什么?
Go over what?
你把毒品交给我 我付你钱
You drop off the coke, I give you the money.
对你来说很难吗?
Is that too much for you to handle?
不是!
No!
不 非常简单 伙计
No, that's totally cool, man.
最好是
It'd better be.
喂
Yeah.
杰克 我是米歇尔
Jack, it's Michelle.
我们查出了那具感染病毒尸体大卫·戈斯
We've got the last known address on David Goss,
已知的最近期的住址
the infected body that was dropped off at Health Services.
多久前的?
How recent?
两个月前
Two months.
好 洛杉矶警局派人去了吗
Okay. Have LAPD send over perimeter team.
告诉他们 蔡斯和我到之前不要采取行动
Tell them hands off until Chase and I get there.
明白
Got it.
蔡斯 出发
Chase, let's go around.
查到地址了?
You get an address?
对
Yeah.
通知他们
Make sure they understand.
杰克到之前不许行动
They are not to go in until Jack gets there, ok?
喂! 皮特说你刚查到了有关戈斯的地址?
Hey! Peter just told me you've got an address on Goss?
是的 我通知杰克了
Yeah. I'm bringing it over to Jack now.
你确定没有更近期的地址了?
You're sure there's nothing more recent?
可以再花一小时找 但不保证能找到更有用的
We could spend another hour looking, but there's no guarantee we find anything better.
嗯 我们没时间可浪费了 打开杰克和蔡斯的通话器
Yeah, we don't have one hour to waste, do we? Look, put transmitters on Jack and Chase.
我要分析他俩的行动 以即时做决策
I wanna be analizing all their interactions so we can work it up in real time, all right?
是
Ok.
杰克
Jack.
有什么事?
What have you got?
这是我们在戈斯身上找到的 这是他贩毒被捕的地址
This is everything we have on Goss. Here is the address where he was arrested for dealing.
多久前的?
How recent?
两个月前 资料都在上面 你可以在路上看看
Two months ago. It's all on the file, you can check it on the way.
很好
Good.
-这是卫生部为你们提供的医疗配件  -谢谢 孩子
-Medical kit that health services has put together for you.  -Thanks, baby.
小心点
Be careful.
出发 蔡斯!
Let's go, Chase!
到那儿弄清楚情况 再行动
We've gonna have to wait until we get there to see what the set-up is.
洛杉矶警局已经包围了那儿
LAPD is locking it down now.
金跟你说了我们的事
And I know Kim told you about us.
我想亲自告诉你 但找不到时机
I was going to tell you myself, I just couldn't find the right time.
你应该知道 我们是认真的
I thought you should know. It's getting serious.
她也是这样说的
That's what she said.
反恐小组怎么说?
What does the CTU have to say?
他们说这可能会是场严重的危机
That it could be a very dangerous situation.
阿尔梅达给了我病毒扩散的后果分析 非常可怕
Almeida sent me a breakdown of what could happen if this virus is released and it's not good.
授予反恐小组全权处理
Give CTU carte blanche.
-满足他们的一切需要  -我已经这样做了
-Whatever they need, make sure they get it.  -I did.
我们应该取消辩论
We should cancel the debate.
什么?
What?
国家正遭受即将发生的生化威胁
It's a mistake to continue preparing for tonight
还继续准备今晚的辩论是错误的
while there is an imminent bio-terrorist threat against this country.
首先 并不确定事情即将发生 大卫
First of all, we don't know that is imminent, David.
再次 你我都知道 我们每天都受到威胁
And you know just as well as I do that we get threats everyday.
但都不像这次
Not like this one.
尸体感染了武器化的病毒
They said the body was infected with a weaponized virus.
好吧 你是对的
Ok, let's say you're right.
即使你把精力放到这事上面 你又能做什么?
What do really think you could do if you put your full attention on it?
我只想确定 你不劝我取消辩论会 是怕我的形像受损
I just wanna make sure that you're not advising me how to fear that my image will suffer if we cancel.
当然会有损害
Oh no, it will suffer.
我认为最好还是按计划举行 有了新情况再作反应
But I still think the best thing to do is to proceed as planned and respond when we have more information.
基勒来了
Keeler's here.
我们换条路走
Come on, let's go this way.
别担心 韦恩
Don't worry, Wayne.
约翰!
John!
总统阁下 你不用专程下来迎接我
Mr.President. You don't have to come away down here just to welcome me.
不麻烦
No, it's no trouble.
在昨天的基金会上 我和你老朋友雅各布·薇姿聊过了
I spoke with your old friend Jacob Weisz yesterday at a fund raiser.
你在南达科塔停留过?
You stopped at South Dakota?
吃顿饭罢了
Just for dinner.
他怎么样?
How is he feeling?
好多了 他还玩了几轮高尔夫
Better. Much better. He's even playing a few rounds of golf.
他就是这样
That's him.
好了 不多聊了约翰
Well, I don't wanna keep you John.
我知道要赢得辩论 你还得去抱抱佛脚
I know you have a lot of last minute cramming to do if you wanna survive this debate.
我不想在这儿跟你辩 总统阁下
I woon't argue with you there, Mr.President.
你的参谋团 你受到纳税人的好评 比我多 三比一
Your resource staff, compliments of the tax payers, outnumbers mine, three to one.
我还得自己出钱请这些人!
I actually have to pay some of them myself!
握手吧?
To shake?
里面见 阁下
I'll see you inside, sir.
当然 先生
You certainly will, sir.
韦恩 我们准备好了
Wayne, we're ready.
你跟他说了什么?
What were you talking to him about?
我们有机会了
I think we may have a opportunity.
什么机会?
What kind of opportunity?
呆会儿再说
Not now, after.
如果你觉得我配不上你女儿 我很抱歉
I'm sorry if you think I'm not good enough for your daughter.
好吗? 但我情不自禁
Ok? But I can't help the way I feel.
蔡斯 你觉得我为什么让金到反恐组工作?
Chase, what do you think I put Kim at CTU?
坐在桌子旁 用电脑工作?
Behind a desk, working on a computer?
这样我就能照看她 确保她的安全!
So I can keep an eye on her, make sure she's safe!
不是让她和外勤探员谈恋爱!
Not so she can start dating some field agent!
安全?
Safe?
你把说得她好像12岁小孩 她是个成年人
You know you're talking about her like she's 12 years old. She's a grown woman.
见鬼 蔡斯 你知道这工作的下场
Damn it Chase, you've seen what this job can do to you.
看看我的下场 它毁掉了我的亲情爱情!
You've seen what it's done to me. It ruined every relationship I ever had!
-是你的问题 杰克...  -不!
-That's you, Jack...  -No!
不 是工作的问题!
No, it's the job!
我不觉得
I don't think so.
你不觉得... 你知道个屁?
You don't think so... What the hell do you know?
因为这工作 我妻子死了
My wife died because of this job.
我差点失去了金  我不会让这一切再发生了
And I almost lost Kim too. I'm not gonna let that happen again.
我会不惜一切保护她 明白吗? 不惜一切!
I will do everything I have to to protect her. Do you understand me? Everything!
见鬼 蔡斯 做这份工作你就不能享有正常生活
Damn it Chase, you cannot have a normal life and do this job at the same time.
你是说我不该和任何人恋爱?
So, you're saying that I shouldn't have any relationship with anyone?
我就这意思
That's exactly what I'm saying.
尤其不能和我女儿
And especially with my daughter.
我是鲍尔探员?
Agent Bauer?
杰克 我是路易斯
Jack, it's Luis.
什么事?
What's up?
我想把萨拉扎带去隔离区 可是总部却进行了一级防范封锁
You tell me. I've tried to move Salazar back to solitary but there is a lockdown from Division.
这是怎么回事?
What's that all about?
我现在不能说
I can't tell you right now.
杰克 这杂狗种当着我们的面杀了他律师
Jack, the bastard murdered his attorney right in front of us.
为什么监狱还在保护他?
What the hell is Division doing protecting him?
他们不是在保护他
They're not protecting him.
那是什么?
Then what?
我现在不想谈这个
I can't get into it right now.
不想谈?
Can't get into it?
拼了命去逮住他的人 不是只有你一个!
You're not the only one who gave up a chunk of his life to put this guy away!
让我了解情况 杰克!
I need to be in the loop Jack!
这消息你可不要告诉其它人
This information doesn't go anywhere after you hang up the phone.
什么消息?
What?
萨拉扎可能会被带走
Salazar might walk.
带走?
Walk?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
听着 还不太清楚 但有人在外面策划行动
Look, I don't think it's gonna get to that. But someone on the outside has got a lot of leverage.
谁?
Who?
我想是他兄弟赫克托
I think it's his brother, Hector.
我不信!
I don't believe this!
-保持警惕 我会尽快打给你  -好的
-Just hang tight. I'll get back to you as soon as I can.  -Yeah. All right.
想想到了那儿 我们该如何行动 呆会我们商量一下
You'd better start thinking about what we're gonna do when we get there. We'll talk about this later.
好
Fine.
开门 我们走
Open the door. Let's go.
-开12号监门  -是
-Open 12.  -Copy that.
不 还没给你找到新律师
No, I haven't found your new lawyer.
等到处决你时再说吧?
About an execution day?
哦! 有人不高兴?
Uh! Someone's not happy?
你知道些什么 拉姆?
What do you know, Ramon?
什么?
About?
-告诉我  -告诉你什么?
-Talk to me.  -Talk to you about what?
你兄弟想干嘛?
What is your brother trying to do?
赫克托? 你有他的消息? 他怎么样了?
Hector? Have you heard from him? How is he?
下周是他的生日 我还不知道送什么给他呢
His birthday's coming up next week. I don't even know what to get him.
你在说废话 伙计
You keep talking trash, man.
你出不了这监狱!
You're not going anywhere!
这可说不定!
Maybe not!
有件事我可以向你保证:
But let me insure you of one thing:
如果发生了什么事 我获得了自由
If something does happen and I am unexpectedly allowed to go free,
我肯定你会来找我
I have no doubt that you'll come looking for me.
尤其是你妻子伊莉斯死后
Especially after the death of your wife, Elise.
还有你两个儿子 叫什么来着? 托马斯和小路易斯?
And your two boys, what are their names? Thomas and Luis Junior?
-恐怖分子又打过电话吗?  -没有
-Any follow-up phone calls from the terrorists?  -No.
所以没什么新情况要向总统汇报?
So basically, there's nothing new to report to the President?
在等鲍尔的消息 他正在追查一条线索
Not until I hear from Bauer. He's following a lead right now.
很好 托尼 谢谢
All right, Tony. Thanks.
今晚辩论后我再接受采访好吗? 谢谢
So, if you excuse me until this evening's debate? Thank you.
进行得挺顺利
That went well.
是的 有新消息吗?
Yes, it did. So, what's the latest?
还没有 反恐小组正在跟踪线索 查找尸体是谁抛下的
Nothing yet. CTU is working a lead. Trying to figure out who dropped off the dead body.
还不知道幕后主谋?
So, they still don't know who's behind this threat?
嗯 他们仍然怀疑萨拉扎的兄弟赫克托
No, they're still speculating on Salazar's brother, Hector.
他们还不知道释放萨拉扎是不是幌子
What they don't know is if it's a bluff staged to release Salazar.
怎么是幌子? 病毒可是切实存在的
And how can it be a bluff? The virus has been confirmed.
是的 抛尸是一件事 大卫 传染一个城市是另一件
Yes but dropping off a dead body is one thing, David. Being able to infect an entire city,
完全不同的事
that's something different.
-好吧 很快我们就清楚了  -好
-All right. I guess we'll know soon enough.  -OK
喂! 韦恩
Hey! Wayne.
你之前提到一个机会
You spoke earlier about an opportunity.
是的... 我还不太确定 我们现在谈谈吧
Yeah... Yeah but I'm not really sure that's something we need to discuss right now.
就是说...
Which means...
因为怕失败 或怕我不喜欢 所以你瞒着我做事
whatever it is fell through or you know I'm not going to like it so you're proceding without me.
不是这样 出了这样的威胁 我不想分散你的注意力
No, that's not it. I just think that because of this threat, I don't wanna divert your attention.
这像边散步边嚼口香糖一样简单 倒底什么事?
Like walk and chew gum at the same time. What is it?
基勒的剧本
Keeler's playbook.
如果我们弄到一份?
What if I can get us a copy?
"剧本"是什么意思?
What exactly do you mean by "playbook"?
今晚辩论他准备的所有文稿
His entire prep for tonight's debate.
他将如何答问 会提出什么问题 一切
How's he gonna answer the questions, what issues he's gonna try to review up on. Everything.
怎么弄得到?
And how would we get it?
你不需要知道细节
You don't need to know the details.
我非常吃惊
I'm surprised.
吃什么惊?
About what?
你知道无论如何 我都不允许这样的事发生
The question. You know there's no way on Earth that I would ever agree to this.
大卫 我... 我不是要喝醉了去偷剧本
David I'm not... I am not talking about pulling a sherry and stealing it.
如果我们只是不小心捡到 为什么不翻翻看?
Now it may just drop in our laps. And if it does why shouldn't we look at it?
韦恩 你不再是我的私人助理了
Wayne, you are not in the private sector anymore.
你应该知道我的内阁是如何工作的
You have to get use to how my administration works.
我在帮助你的内阁得到另一个四年
And I'm just trying to give your administration 4 more years.
好... 好吧 如果你真想这样
Ok... Ok, if that's how you want it.
我是想这样
That's how I want it.
喂! 金 你们都清楚了吗?
Hey! Kim, you are all caught up?
很清楚 我要更新我爸小组的数据
Pretty much. I just have to refresh the data of my dad's panel.
很好
Great.
我能问一件关于你和托尼的事吗?
Can I ask you a question about you and Tony?
我和托尼的什么事?
Me and Tony what?
我不知道 我只是在想...
I don't know, I was just wondering is it...
和丈夫在同一办公室工作有问题么?
a problem working with your husband in the same office?
不 并没有问题 为什么这样问?
No, no, it's... not a problem. Why do you ask?
不是重要的事
It's not a big deal.
没关系 我们还有点空
No, it's ok, we have a minute.
我和蔡斯在交往 但我爸可能不太高兴
Well, I've been dating Chase and I don't think my dad's too happy about it.
我明白了 这...
I see. Well...
我相信你爸只是想保护你...
I'm sure your dad is just trying to protect you but...
不过 这最终是你和蔡斯之间的问题
ultimately, it's just between you and Chase.
我知道了
Yeah, I know.
更新完了告诉我一声 好吗?
Right, let me know when you finish those panels, ok?
好的
Sure.
分析专家刚打来电话
Analysits just called.
他们断定如果赫克托要策划这起生化威胁
They determined that if Hector Salazar is orchestrating this bio-threat,
他很可能是在墨西哥北部进行操纵
he's probably operating in the Northen Mexico.
所以我们需要他在那边的财产目录
So, we're gonna need a list of his properties down there.
克萝伊正在调查 她会检查杰克递交的文件
Chloe's working on it, she's going through the brief files that Jack turned in after the bust.
很好 我去跟她谈
All right. I'll talk to her.
还有...
Also...
联络我们所有的眼线 也许赫克托
Fire up all our contacts and just in case Hector was stupid
蠢得在最近几天出现过呢 懂吗?
enough to show his face in the last couple days, all right?
好
Ok.
那男孩没出乱子吧?
Is the boy still in place?
嗯
Yeah.
总统收到消息了吗?
And the President has been informed?
是的 但他没有取消辩论
Yeah and he's not cancelling the debate.
他真有"胆量" 我来试试他
He's got some 'cojones', I'll give him that.
看看扯上几百万人的性命 他倒底有多强硬
Let's see what kind of tough guy he is when there's a couple of million lives in the line.
克劳迪娅!
Claudia!
-怎么了?  -没事 一切都好
-What's going on?  -Nothing. Everything's fine.
别跟我打马虎眼儿! 你跟你爸吵什么?
Don't tell me nothing! Why are you arguing with your father?
别这样 赫克托 没什么事
Please, Hector, it doesn't matter.
他不喜欢我现在的生活方式
He's not happy with how I live my life.
他不喜欢你跟我在一起?
You mean he doesn't like you being with me?
不许再对你父亲大声吼叫
Don't raise your voice to your father ever again.
克劳迪娅 住手!
Claudia, no!
我怎样对我父亲是我的事 不是你的事!
How I conduct myself with my father is my concern. Not yours!
很好 你说的
Good. Now that's said.
叫露西娅准备晚餐好吗?
Tell Lucia and to prepare supper, ok?
好 我去告诉他
Ok, I'll tell him.
-我是阿尔梅达  -托尼 我是克萝伊 刚接到杰克的电话 他们到了
-Almeida  -Tony, it's Chloe. I just get off the phone with Jack. They've just arrived.
很好 有事吗?
All right, is there a problem?
杰克不使用通话器
Jack's not going to use the transmitters.
为什么?
Why not?
他说接通电源太费事
He says that would take too long to wire them up.
听着 你从他那里收到任何新情况 马上通知我 明白吗?
Whatever. Look, you're learning point from his side, any information he digs up I want it right away. You got it?
行 但你用不着冲我吼
Ok, you don't have to yell.
我没冲你吼 克萝伊
No one's yelling, Chloe.
听着 我们收到了感染可怕病毒的尸体
Look, we got a body infected with a deadly virus.
在接下来的三小时 它和萨拉扎紧密相关
Somehow, we have to tie it to Salazar in the next 3 hours.
现在 杰克所在的地方是我们唯一的线索
Right now, Jack's location is our only lead.
所以有消息你必须及时通知我 懂吗?
So, I need you to keep me up to the minute. Understood?
-我说了没问题  -好 开工吧
-I already said ok.  -Good, then get on it.
费舍尔探长
Detective Fisher.
嗯 你是鲍尔?
Yeah, you're Bauer?
是 他是我搭档蔡斯·埃德蒙兹
Yeah. He's my partner, Chase Edmunds.
情况怎样?
What's the activity?
我们到达后 就没有人进出过
No one's get in and out since we got here.
人手怎样安排的
How is the inside layout.
共30人 分布在各个楼层
About 30 people total, spread out on all floors.
疑犯的公寓 位于三楼转角处
The apartment you asked the case is the corner one there on the third floor.
你们还没进去过吧?
You didn't go in there, right?
我接到命令 你来之前不采取行动
I was ordered to stand down until you got there.
-很好  -你需要多少帮手?
-Good.  -How much back-up you want?
不用 你的人只需要把住出口
None. Right now I want your men just to cover the exits.
不用? 我们带了30个兄弟啊
None? There's 30 scumbags in there.
嗯 我们不想引起任何警觉
Yeah, we don't want to set off any alarms.
我们两人可以溜进去 不会引人注意
Two of us can sneak in without a fight.
你确定?
You're sure about that?
对 打开1号线 需要你们进来时会通知你
Yeah. Get this open on channel 1, we'll let you know when we want you to come in.
你准备好了吗?
You're ready?
上吧
Let's go.
好的
You got it.
这可不是公共楼梯?
The stair is not open to the public?
别紧张 老兄 我们不是来找乐子的
Just take it easy, sport. We're not here to take anybody down.
我们是来了解情况的
We just want a little information.
有人来了!
They come!
蔡斯!
Chase!
退后!
Get back!
上!
Come on!
蔡斯 有个人逃了!
Chase, we got a runner!
休想逃!
Don't even think about it!
我是无辜的 我什么都没做过!
I'm clean, I've got nothing on me!
闭嘴 蠢猪!
Shut up, stupid!
你刚才朝联邦探员开了枪
You've just fired a federal agent.
你最好老实交待
You'd better start talking to me.
不然就让你在这楼梯口流血至死
Or I will let you bleed to death right here on this landing.
蔡斯! 我抓住他了 在楼下!
Chase! I got him, we're down there!
费舍尔 我们抓住嫌犯了
Hey Fisher, we got him. We got our suspect.
-大卫·戈斯是什么人?  -戈斯是毒贩 我从他那买过货
-Who is David Goss?  -Goss is a dealer, I just score from him sometimes.
现在可不是 他已经死了
Well not anymore. He's dead.
好吧 他死了
Ok, he's dead.
给我老实点
Don't be a smartass.
谁供给他毒品? 谁供给他毒品?
Who is his supplier? Who is his supplier?
蔡斯!
Chase!
一个叫卡洛斯·克雷特加的人 在提华纳工作!
A guy Carlos Corretja, he works in Tijuana!
克雷特加是萨拉扎的中层分销商之一
Corretja is one of Salazar's mid-level distributors.
你和他有往来吗?
You're doing business with him?
我今晚要给他打电话
I'm supposed to call him tonight.
克雷特加要我给他找个没前科的人
Corretja wanted me to find a mule, someone clean without a record.
什么目的?
What for?
帮他把一小袋毒品带入境
He wanted to move a small bag of coke across the border.
-但我觉得这样做没意义  -为什么?
-It didn't make any sense to me!  -Why not?
他花一万美元就为了让毒品入境
He payed $10,000 to bring it up.
毒品本身还不值那个价
Coke isn't even worth that much.
-那包毒品在哪里?  -还在那个把它带入境的人手里
-Where's the bag of coke now?  -The guy who brought it across still has it.
-他叫什么名字?  -他叫凯尔·辛格勒
-What's his name?  -His name is Kyle, Kyle Singer.
抱歉海伦 生意归生意...
Sorry Helen, it's business...
这... 这是什么?
What is... What is this?
最后通知
It's a final announce.
如果明早八点半不付房租 我会叫城市服务中心赶走你们
If you don't pay the rent by tomorrow morning 8 am, I'm calling city services and they start the eviction process.
别... 别这样 求你了! 宽限几天吧
Don... Don't do this, no please! I'm gonna have it in a couple of days.
我可不管
I can't take care of you.
我马上回来
I'll get back.
你欠他多少 妈?
How much you own him, 'ma?
-你不用管  -多少?
-Stay out of this.  -How much?
800美元 你不用担心 你爸会去找你叔叔
$800. But don't you worry about it because your father is gonna talk to uncle Stanford.
喂! 800美元 是吗?
Hey! $800, right?
以后有问题 找我或我爸 好吗?
And frpm now, if you have a problem, talk to me or my dad. Ok?
不要找我妈妈
Leave my mum out of it.
最好写信来
I expect your receive in the mailbox.
你哪儿来的钱?
Where did you get that money?
这不重要 好吗? 我们需要钱
It doesn't matter. Ok? We needed it.
我来搞定
I got it.
各位请注意
Can I have everybody's attention, please?
所有人都调查一个叫凯尔·辛格勒的人
Everyone should be working on the name Kyle Singer.
5分钟后希望能在我办公桌上 看到他的主要资料
All right, I want points chief from department's heads on my desk in the next 5 minutes.
集中力量调查凯尔·辛格勒
Everything there is to know about Kyle Singer,
我需要
I want it.
他的住址 职业
Where he lives, where he works,
最重要的是 他现在可能在哪里
and most importantly, where he's likely to be right now.
同外勤保持联系 以便克萝伊分析杰克发回的情况
Also, keep an open channel to Fields Ops so that Chloe can forward anything that comes in back to Jack.
开工!
All right. Let's go!
-你在干嘛?  -缩小搜查范围
-What are you doing?  -Narrowing the search space.
没想到你这么糊涂 凯尔
I can't believe you're so stupid, Kyle.
为了帮补家里?
So, this is how you're gonna help your family?
去贩毒?
By dealing drugs?
不是贩毒 送毒而已 能很快挣到一笔钱给家里
I'm not dealing them. Stupid delivery. It's quick money which my folks need right now.
你家里又上哪儿找钱保释你呢 凯尔?
But where they're gonna get the money to bail you out of jail, Kyle?
你是对的
Ok, you're right.
我知道我糊涂
It's stupid. I know that.
但已经做了
But I did it.
我已经卷进去了
And I'm in this now.
卷进去了...
I'm in the middle of this...
我今晚会去交货 知道吗?
Look, I'll make this delivery tonight. All right?
我保证 今后再也不会了!
I promise, it's gonna be over. I promise you!
等不到今晚了 我们结束了
I'm not waiting until tonight, it's over now.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
我不能和干这勾当的人交往
I can't be with someone who does stuff like this.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
琳达!
Linda!
琳达 别这样
Linda, please.
结束了 凯尔
Over, Kyle.
发生了什么事?
Are you gonna tell me what's going on?
没什么 就是吵了一架
We just have a little disagreement, that's all.
付多恩的房钱是从哪儿来的?
Where did you get the money to pay Don?
妈 别管它 拜托
Mum, forget about it, please.
你爸知道后会怎样?
What's your dad gonna say when he finds out?
一句"别管它"可敷衍不了他
He's not gonna take "forget about it" as an aswer.
我不知道
I don't know.
让我们单独聊聊好吗?
Would you excuse us, please?
抱歉 安妮 今天的行程有些耽误
I'm sorry, Anne. Our schedule has been way off today.
没关系! 我以为你不能来...
No! I think you were unable to join me so...
不会 我能抽出点时间
I am not. I have a couple of minutes.
我提升了你的安全级别
I'm having your security level upgraded.
我想听听你的看法
I'm gonna need your advice today.
怎么了?
What's going on?
你知道3号类型免疫病毒吗?
What do you know about type 3 immuno-viruses?
知道一些 很新的病毒
Not a lot, they're fairly new.
有几类特种 大部分具有快速传染性和致死性
As far as I know there are several strains, most of them fast acting and all are deadly.
有人威胁要在洛杉矶散播此病毒
Someone's threatening to release a virus here in L.A.
天啊!
Oh God!
我要和卫生部的桑尼 马切尔博士讲话
I need to talk to a Doctor Sunny Macer at National Health Services.
嗯 我... 知道桑尼
Yeah, I know... I know Sunny.
大卫 你不觉得此事的可能性很小吗?
But David, don't you think there's a remote possiblity that this thing is for real?
你需要离开洛杉矶
You need to get out of Los Angeles.
那不可能
That's not possible.
辩论会还有两个多小时
The debate is in little over two hours.
别再提辩论会了
No, don't tell me about the debate.
我们在谈这个城市的突发事件
We're talking about an outbreak here in the city.
卫生部没法保护你
This isn't something the Secret Service can't protect you against this.
我... 我知道安妮 如果形势需要我们就离开
I know... I know Anne. We are prepared to leave if the situation warrants it.
但现在 我需要你同桑尼 马切尔谈谈
But right now, I need you to talk to Dr. Sunny Macer
全面了解此事
and learn everything you can about this thing.
好的
I will.
没事的 没事的
That's ok, that's all right.
你弟弟想和你谈谈 阁下
Your brother would like to speak with you, sir.
好 让他进来
Well, send him in.
他在楼下 他让你去找他
He's downstairs. He requests that you come see him.
我去找他?
Come see him?
是的 阁下 他在楼下有东西给你看
Yes, sir. He has something to show you down there.
你去吧 我打给桑尼
You go ahead, I'm gonna call Sunny.
再见
See you later.
不 我会亲自去检查
No, I'm gonna check that out myself.
蔡斯会把疑犯带回去 给他安排一间休息室
Chase is bringing the suspect in the CTU. I want you to set up a wait room for him now.
把帕克带回反恐小组
I need you to take Parker down to CTU.
那凯尔·辛格勒怎么办?
What about Kyle Singer?
我去处理辛格勒 你处理帕克
I'm gonna take care of Singer. I want you to take care of Parker.
可以让其它人把他带回去 我去帮你抓辛格勒
Anybody can take him at CTU and set him up, I'm going with you to get Singer.
不行
No, you're not.
为什么想甩掉我?
Why are you trying to get rid of me?
我不是在甩掉你
I'm not trying to get rid of you.
我认为帕克还有很多情报 你要让他招供
I still think that Parker's got more information and I want you to get it out of him.
因为金吗?
Is this about Kim?
你惩罚我 因为我和她交往?
Are you punishing me for dating your daughter?
听着
You listen to me.
那孩子不知道自己 带着包有病毒的毒品 倒处乱跑
That kid is walking around a bag of cocaine that's got the virus and he doesn't know it.
我得找到他 阻止他传播病毒
I need to find him and stop him from putting it into circulation.
我知道 所以我才想帮你
Yeah, I know. That's why I wanna help you.
不行 太危险
But you can't, it's too dangerous.
太危险?
Too dangerous?
事情可以两全齐美 蔡斯
You can have a both ways, Chase.
我女儿爱你 你想和她一起?
My daughter loves you, you wanna be with her?
那我就必须保障你的安全
Then, I have to stop putting you in harm's way.
你在开玩笑?
You're kidding, right?
把帕克带回局里 这是命令
Take Parker to CTU, that's an order.
好 我再打给你
Yeah. I call you right back.
请让我们单独谈谈
Excuse us for a minute.
怎么了 韦恩?
What is it, Wayne?
别生气 大卫 我拿到了基勒的剧本
Don't be angry, David, but I got a copy of Keeler's playbook.
见鬼! 叫你别这么干!
Damn it! I told you to drop that!
听我说 你不想用可以不用
You just listen to me. If you don't wanna use it then don't.
但有些内容需要看看
But there is something you need to see.
没什么需要看的
There's nothing I need to see.
关于安妮的
It's about Anne.
基勒很聪明 不会打出人种牌或女友牌
Keeler is too smart to play the race card or the girlfriend card.
不是你想的那样 所以我带来给你看看
It's not the one of those which is why I'm bringing this to you.
是她一些我们不知道的事情
It's something that we didn't know about her.
如果是真的...
Something that, if true, could...
大卫 会毁了我们大家
David, it could damage all of us.
看看吧
Just take a look at it.
喂
Yeah.
给我最新情况
Give me an update.
凯尔还在家里
Kyle is still in his house.
货呢?
What about the package?
他手上
It's with him.
拉姆呢?
And Ramon?
正等着回家呢
Just waiting to come home.
很好
Good.
盖尔 你在这儿
Gael, there you are.
克萝伊在找你
Chloe has been looking for you.
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
她在资讯部
She's in I.T.
很好
All right.